Kostadis: Hello.
Gary: So it's not that early.
Gary: Like the sun's out.
Kostadis: 7 a.m.
Wade: That is some glare.
Kostadis: I'm sorry.
Wade: Oh, I mean, it's only 100 nits over here.
Gary: You know, it creates a nice visual effect, though.
Wade: That's a torso shot then.
Wade: Oh, man.
Wade: When you tilted your camera briefly, I saw that painting or whatever print on the lower part of the wall.
Wade: And I was like, there's somebody sneaking up behind you.
Wade: Other side, but yeah.
Wade: It spits behind your body right now.
Wade: We got a brief glimpse of a guy staring at you.
UNKNOWN: Yeah, that guy.
UNKNOWN: It looked like he was somebody who's about to murder you.
Kostadis: It's an old family friend passed away many years ago.
Wade: Oh, I shouldn't make fun of him then.
Kostadis: Oh, no, you can make fun of him.
Kostadis: I mean, I make fun of him.
Kostadis: I just find it funny that that's what you thought, because that is actually a very accurate description of the kind of character he created.
Kostadis: He was a character.
Kostadis: Oh, my God, was he a character?
Kostadis: How's the dog?
Wade: Belligerent.
Wade: Just jumping away at me.
UNKNOWN: Oh, no, I'm getting eaten alive.
UNKNOWN: Oh, the humanity.
Wade: He's all right.
Wade: I had to get one of those little razor scooters just to help desensitize him to that kind of stuff because he sees anything on wheels and freaks the fuck out.
Wade [?]: Oh, no.
Wade: Now I'm tooling around in the backyard of the little razor scooter, just trying to keep him calm.
Wade: Like, this thing's not going to hurt you.
Wade: He's reactive.
Wade: It's just what you get.
Wade [?]: That was the off button.
Kostadis: Okay.
Kostadis: Now let's see.
Kostadis: I roll 2 beyond.
Gary: So I know I'm late to the party, but I'm still making progress with BG3.
Wade: Oh, no, that's dude.
Wade: Go at your own pace.
Wade: That's the beauty of that game.
Wade: You can play when you want, how you want.
Kostadis: Yeah, absolutely.
Kostadis: So where are you?
Gary: I'm in Act 3.
Gary [?]: Oh, you're pretty far along.
Gary: I have cleared the breath spine, kind of like the area outside of the lower city.
Gary: And I've just gotten access to the lower city.
Gary: And that would be kind of like the next.
Gary: That's the next area.
Dave: You're pretty far along.
Gary [?]: Yeah.
Gary: But I did the prison break.
Gary: Sorry, the prison underneath the keep and rescued the counselor there.
Dave: Oh, the counselor, yeah.
Kostadis: Did you...
Kostadis: And apparently he did not end the game in Act Two.
Kostadis [?]: You mean with the Gail's relic?
Kostadis [?]: Yelgo boom.
Kostadis: He didn't do the Galego boom.
Wade: I mean, you can make Yale Go Boom at a lot of points.
Wade [?]: No, although I heard about that.
Kostadis: It's the speed running.
Dave: Yeah, it's the fastest way to get to the credit screen.
Wade [?]: Well, that or shadow boxing, right?
Wade [?]: Like, well, I did a boxing picture from.
Gary: I got a game over in the interlude between act two and act three by killing the emperor.
Wade [?]: Oh, yeah.
Wade [?]: Yeah.
Wade [?]: I guess I didn't do that.
Dave: Yeah, you can't do that.
Dave: Yeah.
Dave: Don't do that.
Gary: I was hoping that it would trigger something else.
UNKNOWN: What's your relationship with Raphael?
UNKNOWN: I'm just curious.
Wade [?]: Highly suspicious.
Gary: I mean, he offered me a deal.
Gary: I was like, I'm going to investigate better other options.
Wade: We took the deal and reneged, and that is a fight.
Wade: It's a very, it's possibly the best, also hardest encounter, I think, in the game.
Dave: You can fight him without reneging.
Dave: You can just go fight him.
Wade: Yeah.
Wade [?]: That is the hardest battle in the game for sure.
UNKNOWN: Is that harder than the reneg fight?
Dave [?]: It's the same fight.
Dave [?]: Oh, it's the same fight.
UNKNOWN: Yeah.
UNKNOWN: I mean, that one was brutal.
UNKNOWN: I don't remember how many times we went through it, but it was also really good.
Wade: I mean, I don't even think you could barrel mans in it because, like, the.
Dave: No, I tried.
Wade: Yeah, I mean, we ended up doing several.
Wade: I think I ended up using Wish.
Wade [?]: We used Wish.
Wade: Yeah, I think.
Wade: Well, my Shadowheart.
Dave: You want to know how I did it?
Wade: How'd you do it?
Dave: Command!
Dave: Command halt over and over again.
Wade: This is why you're on.
Wade: Been wondering what's with all the covers.
Dave [?]: It's the first level spell.
Dave: You can cast it a bunch of times.
Wade: Oh, yeah.
Wade: No, that one was great.
Wade: Other than the, I think the only thing I hated about it, I mean, other than the crippling difficulty, was the music was good the first couple of iterations.
Wade: And then you get really tired.
Dave: Yeah.
Dave: He has his own song.
Wade: Yeah.
UNKNOWN: My monk gets four attacks per round.
UNKNOWN: Nice.
UNKNOWN: Which is good.
Dave: Yeah.
Dave: That's good.
Dave [?]: Four attacks.
Kostadis: Which character?
Kostadis: Which are you playing one of the default characters?
Gary: Monk Thief Tav.
Dave: The Tav.
Gary [?]: You're playing the Tav.
Gary [?]: Yeah.
Kostadis: All right.
Dave: All right.
Dave: Let's do this battle with the Harpies.
Wade [?]: All right.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: I need to get my speaking of Harpies.
Dave: This is very reminiscent of the Baldur's Gate Act 1 Harpy battle.
Dave: Three Harpies.
Dave: Hardy is third level.
Dave: It's pretty much the same thing.
Dave [?]: To make her coffee.
Wade [?]: Do you need to take a minute to make her coffee?
Kostadis: No, no, no.
Kostadis: I'm good.
Wade: We like our GMs, you know, energetic.
Wade [?]: No, no, I'm fine.
Kostadis: I'm just.
Wade [?]: All right.
Kostadis: So, I guess we're starting at the top of the inner ship.
Kostadis: Yes.
Wade: I don't even think we started the first combat run, right?
Wade [?]: We just had.
Kostadis: No, no, no.
Kostadis: The harpy sang.
Kostadis: That's what happened.
Wade: And a couple people got charmed.
Wade [?]: Yes.
Kostadis: Can you put the number one and two for the two harpies that have charmed people?
Gary [?]: Like, next to Valphine and let me just make sure I remember how Harpy songs work.
Gary: So I see if we kill them right here.
Gary: I see charmed in condition.
Kostadis: Yeah, just the guys who are charmed, just if you could just put charmed one.
UNKNOWN: Okay.
Kostadis: Yeah.
Wade: Charmed by one and by two.
Wade: It's not going to matter.
Kostadis: I just need to see if it's an area of effect.
Kostadis: No, it's a target.
Kostadis: So yeah.
Kostadis: Oh, no, it's only one.
Kostadis: Just put Harpy one.
Kostadis: Sorry.
Wade [?]: Only one was singing.
Kostadis: Well, yeah, because it can affect everybody in the 300-foot yard that they see.
Kostadis: Okay, so Harpy's charming.
Dave [?]: Harpy.
Kostadis: A Harpy 3 rather.
Kostadis: Let me put that.
Kostadis: I'll fix it now.
Kostadis: Now that I know what's going on, I will fix it.
Kostadis: Charmed.
Dave [?]: Charm three.
UNKNOWN: Oh.
Dave [?]: All right.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: Okay.
Kostadis: So,
Kostadis: Viva Las Vegas, folks.
Kostadis: You're up.
Wade: Oh, shoot.
Wade [?]: Wrong speaker.
Dave: Like I said, it's not going to matter.
Dave: Silence.
Dave: That should eliminate the charm condition.
Wade [?]: I already sound can be created.
Dave: I put the 20-foot radius on the screen there for you.
Gary: That's good.
Kostadis: Hold on.
Kostadis: Oh, boo beef.
Wade [?]: Good bard.
Wade [?]: I did something useful.
Wade [?]: You'd be useful.
Wade [?]: I'm complimenting you.
Wade [?]: Good part.
Kostadis: All right.
Dave [?]: So you did, you put it in a 20-foot yard, a 20-foot orange sphere here.
Dave [?]: All right.
Dave [?]: Okay.
Wade [?]: It looks like a circle, but it's a sphere in 3D.
Wade [?]: Just got to rotate it.
UNKNOWN: Yeah.
Kostadis: Is it a 20-foot radius or 20-foot square?
Dave: 20-foot radius.
Dave: Oh, even bigger.
Dave: Wow.
Dave: Okay.
Gary [?]: That's it.
Dave: Then I can move it a little bit here.
Dave: Somehow, yours is bigger than mine.
Dave: Are you sure yours is the right size?
Kostadis: It says 20-foot radius.
Dave: It does say that, but.
Dave: Oh, it's not the blue.
Wade [?]: It's the border.
Dave: Okay.
Dave: I can't move that, though.
Dave: Can you give me control of that shape?
Dave [?]: Oh, I can only do center to center.
Wade [?]: Oh, there I go.
Wade [?]: There we go.
Wade [?]: So more like.
Wade: Hey, that's a little bigger than 20-foot.
Wade: I'm getting 45.
Wade: It seems bigger than 20 to me, but I see 45 across, not 40, but it's close.
Dave: Yeah.
Kostadis: Or do you want it?
Dave [?]: Like here?
Dave: Probably move it to the left, some.
UNKNOWN: Give us more space toward the door.
Dave: Like that.
Dave: It's pretty good.
Dave: Well, as long as that's enough to cancel the charm condition on both and Valphine.
Wade [?]: Oh, you see.
Dave: Why do I have to count?
Dave: She can sing.
Dave: She can sing all she wants.
Dave: We can't hear her.
Wade: Everyone is deafened inside the circle.
Dave: She can sing if she wants.
Wade [?]: Okay, right, right, right, right.
Wade: We're all deaf.
Dave: Yeah, that's probably optimal right there.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: So you are no longer affected by the charm.
Dave: We can delete charmed.
Dave: As I said, it wasn't going to matter.
Kostadis [?]: All right.
Kostadis [?]: Harpy.
Kostadis: I'm preferring Dave the fighter.
Kostadis: It was a lot easier to have combat.
Dave: I just roll a bunch of dice and say this is really boring.
Dave: Okay, Harpy 1 is up.
Kostadis: What's Harpy 12?
Wade: Sorry.
Kostadis: Oh, that's fine.
Kostadis: Your early morning yawns are contagious across the ocean. He's kind of like and goes over here. Okay, right from us.
Dave: Ran away.
Dave [?]: Okay.
Dave: He ran away.
Kostadis: Yeah, he ran away.
Kostadis: Hold on.
UNKNOWN: Okay.
Kostadis: Yes, it ran away into over the parapet.
Kostadis: Frustrated.
Dave: All right, Soma.
Wade: Yeah.
Wade: You know it's coming.
Wade: Give me a bear icon.
Wade: Actually, that's probably too big to get through this whole thing.
Dave: You're going to have to go through the passageway first, then transform.
Wade: Or I could go into spider mode.
Wade: That'd probably be fine too.
Dave: But you want to have a power attack on Harpy 2, right?
Wade: Okay, let's see.
Wade: My movement is not spider singing.
Wade: Yeah, I think spider is better.
Kostadis: So just to be clear, the folks who made the saving through originally are immune to the harpy song for 24 hours.
Kostadis: The other folks are not.
Dave: Oh, okay.
Dave: So.
Dave: Oh, so I don't have to worry about hiding in the immune to all harpy songs or just the harpy song from Harpy?
Kostadis: Immune to all harpy songs.
Dave: Oh, wow.
Kostadis [?]: Or twelve per day.
Kostadis [?]: All right.
Dave: Oh, so sorry.
Dave: Velphine and Brewbarry could be susceptible.
Kostadis [?]: No, no, no, sorry, to this harpies, not all, not all.
Dave: Yeah, exactly.
UNKNOWN: So if the other harpy sings, they might, you have to re-roll.
UNKNOWN: Yeah, exactly.
Wade: All right, yeah.
Wade: Give me a spider icon that we're going to wild shape into that.
Kostadis [?]: Oh, okay.
Kostadis: Wild spider?
Wade: Yeah.
Wade: Well, for climbing and getting up there.
Wade: You know.
Wade: Whatever.
Wade: I'm, you know, I'll be me.
Wade [?]: I don't know, hold on.
Wade [?]: We got some of the wolf spider.
Wade: Trying to limit the shapes I use.
Kostadis: Why?
Wade: Well, I think technically you're only supposed to have like ones that you're familiar with, right?
Wade: Like, oops.
Wade: Wow, I can move this thing.
UNKNOWN: Well, that's great.
UNKNOWN: I can't move the wolf spider.
Kostadis: I know.
Kostadis: Hold on.
Kostadis: I have to just put it on the other side.
Kostadis: I just change the token.
Kostadis: Okay, there you go.
Wade: Nope.
Wade: It's still grabbing the wrong thing.
Kostadis: Okay, now you should be able to move it.
Wade: Nope.
Wade: Unless it's under the silence thing.
Wade: I'm only grabbing the silence guy.
UNKNOWN: Yeah.
Dave: Send silence to the back.
Kostadis: There.
Kostadis: You should be able to move it now.
Wade: Now I can move neither.
Wade [?]: Oh.
Wade: I can't move the spider doodle.
Dave: Yep.
Kostadis: Whatever.
Wade [?]: No, hold on, hold on.
UNKNOWN: Oh, that's the problem.
UNKNOWN: I didn't.
UNKNOWN: There you go.
UNKNOWN: Now you should be able to move it.
UNKNOWN: Sorry.
Wade: All right.
Kostadis [?]: Yeah.
UNKNOWN: Since I can just kind of, you know, completely ignore difficult terrain or anything, I can just kind of chill out and go this way.
Kostadis: By the way, they're flying, just so you know that they are flying.
Wade: How high?
Kostadis: Well, this one was flying down.
UNKNOWN: So let's see.
Wade: This one saying number two?
Kostadis: Yeah, number two.
Wade: I mean, in theory, I could probably scale this wall next to number two to help get into range, right?
Kostadis [?]: Like, yeah.
Kostadis: Yes.
Wade: I mean, the spider is climby crazy.
Wade: So let's just say I climb the wall then.
Wade: So wherever it is, I'm on top of it.
Kostadis: Okay.
Gary: Does your spider form have a web or anything?
Wade: No, it's just got good mobility and then you know, attacks public roll.
Wade: That's a hit.
Dave: Nice.
Dave: 11 damage.
Wade: And yeah, yep.
Wade: On harpy number oceans.
Dave: Wow, these have a lot of hit points.
Wade: Wow.
Dave [?]: Oh my god.
UNKNOWN: You're not kidding.
UNKNOWN: Yeah, Bear would have been nicer.
UNKNOWN: Oh, well, but then he couldn't get around.
Dave: Yeah.
Kostadis: So strictly speaking, 27.
Kostadis: I hate this map.
Kostadis: Can I just see that?
Wade: Oh, because it's not one of the nice new generated ones or whatever.
Kostadis: Here.
Kostadis: Okay, so just to be clear, this is what you're saying.
UNKNOWN: Since you made it to the upper level.
Wade: Oh, well, I'm climbing in the wall.
Wade [?]: I'm not trying to be in the building, right?
Wade [?]: He's on the exterior.
Kostadis: Yeah, I'm just saying the upper level.
Kostadis: Well, the harpy is on the upper level, so that's that's why I was
Dave [?]: over here.
Dave: Is it 20 feet up?
Dave: How high up is that is the second level?
Dave [?]: Um, these 10 feet.
Dave [?]: Uh, let's see.
Kostadis: Let me see, time of storms.
Kostadis: Um, 10 feet.
Dave: 10 feet.
Dave: Okay.
Kostadis [?]: So you're still inside the sphere.
Dave: I also made myself, you might need to be right about there.
Dave: Like on the corner there, like in order to be inside the sphere.
Wade: Yeah, that's fine.
Wade: That still puts me in melee-ish range.
Dave [?]: I'm just trying to scale the wall to, you know.
Dave: Yeah, so you should still be silent in the silence.
Dave: All right.
Dave: Looks good.
Dave: 11 damage.
Wade: Yep.
Dave [?]: Tracked it.
Dave: Cool.
Kostadis [?]: Brewbarry.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: So you guys can see the upper level, but I'm just going to keep them over there so you guys have some otherwise trying to keep track of whereas everybody is going to be exhausting.
Wade [?]: Hold on.
Wade [?]: I'm going to move my token out of here.
Wade [?]: Get to whatever.
Kostadis: All right.
Gary: You go out of the water.
Gary: So Brewbarry can make it to right here, and then it's just enough range for the hell bird.
Wade: Hi, Katie.
Gary: Bird.
Wade [?]: And then with rage.
Gary [?]: Don't forget to rage.
Gary: And rage, yep.
Gary: 11.
Dave: Oh, does it 10 misses?
Gary: 10 misses.
Gary [?]: Yeah.
Gary: All right.
Gary: So I guess that's it for me.
Gary [?]: Yikes.
Kostadis [?]: When did you get hit?
Kostadis: Your hit points say 11 here.
Kostadis [?]: Oh, that's a mistake.
Kostadis: I think you didn't update it after the last combat.
Dave: Yeah, I fixed it.
Dave: Thank you.
Kostadis: All right.
Dave [?]: Who's up now?
Dave: Harpy 2 is up.
Kostadis: Harpy 2 disengages.
Dave: Really?
Kostadis: Yes.
Kostadis: Well, I mean, the harpies, harpies like to charm their enemies, not they literally know they cannot do it.
Kostadis: Yeah.
Kostadis: I think that's it's kind of like, you know, silent spells are very effective at dissuading harpies from attacking you.
Dave [?]: Okay.
Dave [?]: Interesting.
Kostadis: This is where ranged attacks would be useful.
Wade [?]: Yeah, clearly we're going to need ranged.
Wade: Oh, wait, sorry.
Wade: Didn't we get a disengage on the one that went away from me?
Gary [?]: Oh, did you?
Wade [?]: Yeah, I did.
Wade: Oh, he did disengage.
Wade: Sorry.
Dave: Valphine, you're up.
Wade [?]: All right, then.
Gary: I believe I have a range spell.
Gary: And let's see what this is.
Dave: You can't cast the spell with a verbal component.
Gary: I know.
Gary: Let's see if I can step outside and then come back in or something.
Dave: If you stop outside, then you'll be charmed.
Gary: Well, I'd be charmed the moment I.
Kostadis: Yes.
Gary: Oh, okay.
Gary: Well.
Kostadis: First, you get to roll a saving throw.
Gary [?]: You might make it.
Gary: Oh, I get to roll a saving throw first.
Gary: Okay.
Gary: All right.
Kostadis: No, no, hold on, hold on.
Kostadis: At the end of each of its turns, right, at the end.
Kostadis [?]: Okay.
Gary: So I can shoot it with an arrow, I guess.
Dave: Yeah, you can definitely do.
Dave: Nice.
Dave [?]: Ah, crit.
Gary [?]: Vorticle damage even.
Gary: 4-6.
Kostadis: Who did you do this against?
Gary: Whoever.
Gary: Can I see the one who was trying to charm me?
Kostadis: Yes, this is number three.
Gary: Number three.
Gary: Yes.
Gary: Number three would be the one I would attack.
Kostadis: Okay, so I have to roll a concentration spell.
Kostadis: He makes a concentration, but takes expensive damage.
Gary: Okay, I applied the damage.
Kostadis: You put the damage in?
UNKNOWN: Yep.
Gary: Yep.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: Okay.
Dave: Harpy three.
Kostadis: Let's see.
Kostadis: What does Harpy 3 do?
Kostadis: How intelligent are these things?
Kostadis: They're not particularly intelligent.
Kostadis: Okay, so they would not know about spells.
Kostadis: They would just know that this doesn't.
Dave: They would not know about concentration.
Kostadis: No, you've got an intelligence of seven.
Dave: Okay.
Kostadis: I don't think, I think they would be mostly.
Kostadis: But you did just try to hit it. All right. So we'll come screeching. I've got to get this right. And try to attack you. Valphine. Oh my God. The lag on the computer is all right. What does the harpy do? What is the harpy's attacks? It's one claw attack.
Kostadis: And misses.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: And then it flies away.
Kostadis: You get an attack of opportunity.
Gary [?]: Nice.
Gary [?]: Go for it.
Gary: Aritha.
Gary: Go with.
Gary: Here.
Kostadis: Not you.
Kostadis: Valphine.
Kostadis: She was attacking Valphine.
Dave: Yeah, Valphine, not Brewbarry.
Dave [?]: Wait.
Gary: Valphine gets an attack for opportunity.
Kostadis: Yes, because the Harpy swoops down, strikes, and then flies away.
Gary: Ah, okay.
Gary: Arthur.
Dave: No.
Dave: Roll a five, man.
Dave: You roll a five.
Dave: It's going to be a long, slow battle.
Wade: Well, they're just retreating.
Wade: Maybe we just let them.
Dave: Yeah, so we could roll your saving throw.
Dave: We could just run inside the building, right?
Dave [?]: Yeah, right, yeah.
Kostadis: Saving throw?
Gary [?]: But we have to kill him at some point.
Gary: Wisdom save?
Kostadis: Yeah, yeah, wisdom save.
Gary [?]: Sorry, I missed that.
Gary: I guess Brewbarry gets one as well, right?
Kostadis: Yes.
Gary [?]: By the way, yeah.
Gary: Okay, so Valphine, I assume, saves and is the 13th.
Kostadis: Yep.
Kostadis: Yes, so you're both now no longer charmed.
Kostadis: You're now no longer affected by the charm of that of Harpy number three.
Dave: Which means you can step out of the silence, attack, and go back in.
Dave: As long as another harpy doesn't start singing.
Kostadis: Yeah.
Kostadis: Okay.
Kostadis: Of course, the harpy doesn't know that you've saved.
Dave: Okay.
Dave: So Vukradin is up?
Gary: I think so, yes.
Dave: Okay.
Dave: Um.
Dave: So I can probably go like out here, cast a spell against Harpy 3, and then run back inside, correct?
Kostadis: Yep.
Dave: Okay, so I'll do that.
Kostadis: Yes.
Kostadis: 60 foot range, right?
Dave: Yeah, I mean, it's only 10 foot away, so yeah.
Kostadis [?]: So 60-foot range.
Kostadis [?]: So four damage on three.
Dave: It's down to 28.
Dave: Run back inside.
Kostadis: Okay.
Dave: Lomat.
Dave: Okay, Harpy one.
Dave: Really, just wear them down slowly.
Wade [?]: Harpy one.
Dave [?]: Bottle of attrition.
Kostadis: Harpy one.
Kostadis: V1
Kostadis: flies by
Kostadis: strikes the spider.
Kostadis: The spider.
Kostadis: Hold on.
Kostadis: I don't know if you saw that, but I got 20.
Kostadis: I rolled a 22 and six points of damage.
Kostadis: And the harpy flies away again.
Kostadis: So you get your attack of opportunity.
Kostadis: Excellent.
Kostadis [?]: I mean, it's something.
Wade: Public roll.
Wade: Harpies are 11.
Wade: That's a hit.
Kostadis: Wow.
Kostadis: That's a lot of damage.
Wade: It's 12 damage.
Wade: Dude, Circle of the Moon Druids start early.
Wade: They don't really get better, but they start early.
Wade: That was Harpy 1 gets 12 damage.
Wade: So 26.
Wade: Yeah.
Wade: And you said, sorry, how much damage you say you did to me six?
Kostadis [?]: Yeah.
UNKNOWN: All right, back down to 30.
Wade: And then I guess that makes it my turn.
Dave: Yep, someone's up.
Wade: Presumably, can I get into range of number one by scampering across the wall?
Kostadis: Hold on, let me see.
Dave: You can, but then if you want to flee back, they'll get an attack as you flee.
Wade: Do I want to flee?
Dave: Well, if you don't flee, another harpy might start singing.
Dave [?]: Spiders be charmed?
Kostadis [?]: Okay, sorry.
Dave: That's a fair question.
Wade: I think they can.
Wade: They don't see any signs of immunity.
UNKNOWN: What is your question?
Wade: I was joking.
Wade: Can you charm a spider?
Wade: But of course, I'm sure you can.
Kostadis [?]: Yes.
Wade: Yeah.
Gary: Can you grapple it and then pull it back into the silence?
Kostadis: Well, remember, they don't know who.
Kostadis: Yeah.
Kostadis [?]: I don't know that I could.
Wade: Anyway, I'm just going to go whale on it anyway.
Wade [?]: You're going to race after it?
Wade: I'm going to chase after it.
Wade: I mean, it wants to play this game with me.
Wade: I'll play with it.
Kostadis: All right.
Wade: Camon, public roll.
Wade: All right.
Wade: That was a worthy effort.
Kostadis: Heroic.
UNKNOWN: It would have been a good damage, but oh well.
Wade: Take the attack of opportunity.
Wade: Come at me, bro.
Kostadis: Okay.
Dave: Why can't we see your roles, Costanis?
Kostadis [?]: Do you see them now?
Wade [?]: I see a miss.
UNKNOWN: I see a hell of a miss.
Kostadis: I had to fix the.
Kostadis: There was a setting I had to fix.
Dave [?]: Okay.
Kostadis [?]: All right.
Kostadis [?]: Spider done.
Kostadis [?]: Brewbarry is up.
Gary: All right.
Gary: I assume there's nothing here within range, right?
Dave [?]: No, there's not.
Dave: You don't have any ranged weapons?
Gary: Well, I may have a throwing axe or something.
Gary: Yeah, hand axe.
Wade [?]: Can't scale the walls?
Gary: I might.
Gary: So number one, I could probably hit with a hand axe.
Gary: And can you say more about the altitude of number three?
Kostadis: Number three is it's about the same level as Vukradin, just far away, so he's down 20 feet.
Kostadis: Okay, and my number three, you said.
Gary: Yeah.
Gary: So my range is 20.
Gary: So I'm guessing that I have to go like approximately here to get in range of number one.
Dave [?]: Yeah.
Gary: All right.
Gary: I guess hand axes are cheap, right?
Dave: I heard that.
Dave: Brewbarry's whiffing tonight.
Dave: It's two whiffs.
Kostadis: You do have a second-hand axe, right?
Kostadis [?]: I assume so.
Kostadis: Yeah, you can try it.
Kostadis: You can use it as your bonus action.
Kostadis: I think you have to.
Dave [?]: Is it as a bonus action?
Dave: Yeah, as a light weapon, right?
Dave: Yeah.
Kostadis: Yeah, you can use two light weapons.
Gary: Okay.
Gary: Sure.
Gary: I guess I can throw the second one then.
Dave: Looks about right.
Dave: Yep.
Wade: Hey, consistency, man.
Wade [?]: You can do it.
Dave [?]: The arrows.
Gary: It's the exact same one.
Dave: What does Brewbarry have to say about that?
Dave: Okay.
Dave: Harpy two.
Dave: This very long, slow battle.
Wade: Do you have other plans tonight, Dave?
Dave: I think it's going to be tonight and next week.
Kostadis: You could just run into the castle.
Dave: No, but we could.
Dave: But the point of coming here was to liberate the castle, not just get the treasure, right?
Dave: We're trying to liberate the castle.
Dave: This is what is luring all the ships to be smashed.
Dave: So we have a moral obligation to defeat the harpies.
Kostadis: Oh, right.
Kostadis: Actually, it's the green tower, not the harpies.
Wade [?]: Sorry?
Wade: We don't know that, do we?
Kostadis: Yeah, you do, because what's his name?
Kostadis: That's like the giant crab tool.
Kostadis: Well, I guess you don't know.
Wade: I don't think Krabby McGee told us that.
Kostadis: I don't know.
Kostadis: You're right.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: Okay.
Kostadis: So whose turn is it now?
Dave: Harpy 2.
Kostadis: Harpy 1.
Kostadis [?]: Harpy 2.
Dave [?]: I know Harpy 1.
Dave [?]: Harpy 2.
Kostadis: Harpy 2 is going to start.
Wade [?]: Harpy 2 is convinced that the problem was the other guy's song, so it's starting to sing as well.
Wade: Good job.
Dave: Oh, they really are dumb.
Wade: Intelligence 7.
UNKNOWN: That's what you get.
Wade [?]: Very.
Dave: So that'll be an issue if somebody wants to leave the sphere.
Dave: Okay.
Wade [?]: Oh, so if I dart out to now do a saving throw.
Dave: Yeah.
Wade: That is unfortunate.
UNKNOWN: Okay.
Dave [?]: Valphine.
Gary [?]: Excuse me.
Gary: All right.
Gary: So she can, I guess, at least shoot the crossbow at number three again because we need to spread out our damage as much as possible, right?
Kostadis: It's a concentration effect, so you can break their concentration.
Dave: You could shoot at two and try to break concentration on two.
Gary: Two, you say.
Gary: All right.
Gary: Sure.
Gary: I'll do number two.
Kostadis: Okay.
Kostadis: That's good.
Gary: Seven damage on two.
Gary: I'll apply the damage.
Kostadis: And it makes its concentration.
Wade [?]: Ah, fiddle six.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: Who is next?
Dave: RP3.
Kostadis: RP3.
Kostadis: RB3 screeches
Kostadis: comes into range here.
Kostadis [?]: Okay.
Kostadis: And attacks you.
Dave [?]: All right.
Kostadis: Harpy.
Dave: This could be a disaster.
Dave [?]: Or not.
Kostadis: And misses.
UNKNOWN: And misses.
Kostadis: Yes, sir.
Dave: All right.
Dave: I like it.
Wade: Stabby stabby.
Dave: I'll do my attack.
Kostadis: Oh my, you hit.
Dave: I hit and another six damage on three.
Dave: Okay, down to 22.
Kostadis: And it is no longer howling.
Dave [?]: Oh, that one stopped singing.
Dave: Oh, it was singing, and it's no longer singing.
Kostadis [?]: Yeah.
Dave: Okay, but two is still singing.
Dave [?]: Yes.
Dave: All right, Vukradin, what are you going to do?
Dave: You've got no physical ranged attacks, only magical ranged attacks.
Gary: What is the range of the singing?
Kostadis [?]: That's good.
Kostadis: 39 feet.
Kostadis: 300 feet.
Wade [?]: Oh.
Wade: So it really doesn't matter if three stops singing while two is doing it.
Kostadis [?]: Yeah.
Wade: Except, I guess one saving throw protects you from that person indefinitely, that harpy indefinitely.
Wade: Which one was the one that we entered on?
Dave: I'm going to grant myself bardic inspiration, which means I fail a saving throw.
Dave: If I fail a saving throw, then I can use my bardic inspiration die to possibly pass it instead.
Dave: All right.
Dave: And I will take the chance because I don't want this combat to go on forever.
Dave: I will run out here.
Dave: I will make a wisdom saving throw.
Dave [?]: Hello.
Dave [?]: Okay.
UNKNOWN: Which is not good.
UNKNOWN: What is my target?
Kostadis: Number two.
Kostadis [?]: So you're going to start running towards saving DC.
Kostadis: 11-11.
Dave: 11.
Dave: All right.
Dave: I have a good chance, but not 50.
Wade [?]: Not a guaranteed chance of making it.
Wade: 50-50, right?
Wade [?]: Well, no better than that.
Wade [?]: Oh, I thought you had a significant thing.
Dave: It's five and six.
Dave: Five and six of a DC.
Dave: And I made it.
Dave: All right.
Dave: So I turned my failure into a success.
Kostadis: Excellent.
Dave [?]: Amazing.
Dave: And should I.
Kostadis: Wait, hold on.
Kostadis: This is so on character for Vukradin.
Wade: He's failing upward.
Kostadis: No, no, he's turning his failures into successes, right?
Kostadis: I mean, you know.
Dave: And then we're trying to hit two.
Dave: Two is the one that we need to.
Kostadis: Yes.
Kostadis: All right.
Wade: That's the singing one.
Kostadis [?]: Let's hit two.
Kostadis: You can see it.
Kostadis: It's up in the air.
Kostadis: So you can see.
Kostadis [?]: Way over here.
Kostadis [?]: That's a hit.
Dave: That's a hit.
Dave: For seven damage on two.
Kostadis: And the concentration is over.
Kostadis [?]: Excellent.
Dave: Wow.
Dave: I'm having a good combat.
Kostadis [?]: Good job, Vukradin.
Wade [?]: Vukradin using all the abilities for three.
Wade: I guess I can't actually cheer you on because, you know, I'm deafened in the.
Dave: Yeah, you can, you know, make some hand gestures.
Dave: Well, you're a spider.
Wade: I can give you four arms up.
Dave: All right.
Dave: Harpy one.
Kostadis: Harpy one.
Kostadis: Well, seeing how Harpy three and harpy two songs ended, harpy one is now singing.
Wade: Oh, wait.
Wade: Which one was singing when we entered?
Wade: Was it three?
Wade [?]: Yeah, three.
Wade [?]: Okay.
Wade: So I'm immune to three's song, although it's not going to sing again.
Dave: So one is now singing?
Dave: Okay.
Dave [?]: One is now singing.
Dave [?]: Okay.
Dave: Soma.
Wade: Yeah.
Wade: Boy, I'd love to kind of.
Wade: Can I climb down the wall, sort of take a path around so that I end up in range of just one without getting a disengage problem on two?
Kostadis: Yeah, you can go.
UNKNOWN: You can use three dimensions to do that.
Wade: Yeah, so I think I do that because I do want to get in and out potentially.
Wade: So let's say I'm kind of on the edge of the wall underneath him.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: Roll a.
Wade: Yeah, I still have to do the song check.
Kostadis [?]: I got you.
Wade: Yeah, I'm with you, Dave.
Wade: I don't want this to last all night.
Wade: It's wisdom, right?
Dave: I will.
Dave: Oh, oh, no, I can't give you Vardica's correct.
Wade [?]: It's okay.
Wade: I've got a plus five wisdom.
Dave [?]: You made it.
Dave [?]: Yeah, it's okay.
UNKNOWN: He makes the same.
Wade: All right.
Wade: So I don't have to actually.
Kostadis: So Soma's heard better songs.
Wade: Yeah.
Wade: From Vukradin, no.
Wade: From me, probably.
Wade: Exactly.
Wade: All right.
Wade: Let's see if we can't break that concentration.
Kostadis: So I'm branded.
Wade: Let's go.
Wade: Oh, I think that should have only been a plus one, but it's still.
Wade: I should have used the spider's stat, I think.
Dave: I don't see anything.
Wade: It's all right.
Wade: Oh, no.
Wade: I'm just saying the that's eight damage on number one.
UNKNOWN: And check his concentration for me.
Dave: On one.
Wade: Yeah, somebody's getting that for me.
Kostadis: Makes it makes it.
Wade [?]: Makes it.
Wade: Yeah.
Wade: All right.
Kostadis: You are immune.
Kostadis [?]: You are immune from it.
UNKNOWN: Yeah, since two and three won't sing, and I'm immune to one.
Wade: I'm immune to one and three.
Wade: So, yeah, that's fine.
Wade: I'm just going to stay out of the silence bubble now.
Kostadis: Two got a concentration broken, so yeah, I don't know how often they can sing.
Wade: I'm not very familiar with harpies.
Wade: That's okay.
Wade: Anyway, that's it.
Dave: All right, Brewbarry.
Gary [?]: All right.
Gary: Is my option scale the ball?
Wade: You can't cheer it from the silence.
Gary: Is Brewbarry's option here to scale the wall?
Wade: Yes.
Gary: Okay.
Gary: Is that an athletics check?
Wade: Not if you're a spider.
Kostadis: I'm trying to think here.
Kostadis: Give me a sec.
Kostadis: That's just bad artistic rendering.
Wade: Acrobatics or athletics both seem fine.
Kostadis: No, yeah, just a climbing wall.
Kostadis: Athletics or acrobatics.
Kostadis: Doesn't matter which one we want.
Kostadis [?]: Strength one for sure, right?
Wade: Athletics.
Wade [?]: Why do I have advantage on athletics checks?
Dave [?]: Because you are a barbarian.
Wade: You're proficient, right?
Wade [?]: But it has advantage here for some reason.
Dave [?]: It probably does have.
Kostadis: No, no, you can.
Kostadis: This is not a particularly slippery surface.
Kostadis: It's just half your movement.
Gary: What?
Gary: You mean without a check or just half?
Gary [?]: Double movement.
Dave [?]: Double movement.
Kostadis: It's just difficult terrain.
Gary: All right.
Gary: Then I will scale the wall up to the top of the battlement, I guess.
Dave [?]: All right.
Dave: And then use your 10-foot reach.
Wade [?]: Yeah, actually.
Dave: Why don't you step back?
Wade: And then you could potentially cleave number two after hitting one, right?
Dave: Well, if you go there, you're going to have to make a wisdom save.
Dave: If you're five feet back, you could hit two and be safe, not have to make the save.
Gary: Okay.
Gary: I mean, I guess theoretically the silent spell is a sphere, right?
Wade [?]: Oh.
Wade [?]: By the time I get up to the top of the wall, we determined that I was only safe in this square.
Gary [?]: So I don't think you're safe where you're at.
Wade [?]: That's true.
Gary [?]: Well.
Gary: All right, so make your saving term?
Gary: Well, you know, like, I'm not going to do anything else, right?
Wade: Yeah, you may as well.
Wade: I mean, your wisdom's probably not great, but.
Wade: Okay, when I said not great, I didn't mean roll a one.
Dave [?]: Well, it's dismally time.
Wade [?]: It's a two minus one, just to be clear.
Wade: It's a net of a one.
Wade: I don't know.
Wade [?]: It's not quite a zero.
UNKNOWN: Is that what happened here?
Kostadis [?]: You just got charmed.
Gary: And I'm charmed by which one?
Kostadis: Number one.
Kostadis: One.
Dave: One is the one thingy.
Gary [?]: Charmed one.
Gary: Got it.
Gary: Okay.
Gary: Good times.
Gary: RP2.
Kostadis: RP2.
Wade: So, if you're charmed and they end up sending you into the silence, you become deaf and lose charm, right?
Kostadis: Yes.
Dave [?]: Yeah.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: So, harpy number two.
Kostadis: I guess you have an attack of opportunity on harpy number two.
Kostadis: Well, yeah, you do.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: Harpy number two.
Wade: Boomy?
Kostadis: No, no.
Wade: No, I specifically positioned not to be in range of two.
Kostadis: Okay, right.
Wade: I'm on the wall underneath one because I didn't want to get, I was planning on disengaging and then whatever.
Kostadis: Okay, got it.
Kostadis: Okay, harpy number two attacks you.
Kostadis: You have the incapacitated condition when you're charmed.
Kostadis: Well, or rather, you are effectively incapacitated.
Kostadis: I don't know what that gives you.
Kostadis: So let me just.
Wade: Disadvantage on all saving throws of thought, something like that.
Kostadis: Very inconvenient.
Kostadis: You can't take actions or reactions.
Dave: Okay, but normal attack.
Kostadis: It's just a normal attack, yeah.
Dave: Yeah.
Kostadis: And misses.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis [?]: Okay.
Kostadis: Eleven misses, yeah.
Kostadis [?]: Yeah.
Wade [?]: Our lowest AC is 13.
Dave: You can't take actions or reactions, but you can still move.
Kostadis: No, you have to move towards the creature, the harpy that lured you.
Gary: Well, the move is a move action, right?
Kostadis: You already used your move.
Kostadis: I'm assuming you're climbing up.
Dave: Sorry.
Dave: Yeah, that's fine.
Dave: It's fine.
Dave [?]: Okay.
UNKNOWN: Oh, Valphine.
Gary: Valphine.
Gary: All right.
Gary: So she at least has her crossbow, which is the one that's going to be a little bit more.
Gary [?]: Number one is the one that is singing, by the way.
Gary [?]: I just remembered that.
Gary: All right, fine.
Gary: I mean, I'm going to.
Kostadis: Well, I mean, you know, Valphine, this is very odd.
Kostadis: Valphine is showing loyalty to her, you know.
Gary: Because I feel like she'd want to kill the one that's most wounded, right?
Kostadis: Okay, fair, fair, whatever.
Dave: Okay.
Dave: Who took six damage?
Gary: Six piercing on number two.
Dave: Number two?
Gary [?]: Okay.
Gary: That's down to seven.
Gary [?]: Thanks.
Dave [?]: All right.
Kostadis: All right.
Dave: Harpy three.
Kostadis: RP3.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: Harpy three is going to.
Kostadis [?]: Attack the bard.
Kostadis: Let's attack the bard.
Dave: Okay.
Wade: Spiders running around the walls, chomping on all their likes.
Dave [?]: Sounds good.
Kostadis [?]: Sounds good.
Kostadis [?]: It's a hit.
UNKNOWN: So 12 damage on me.
Dave: Down to nine.
Dave: All right.
Dave: And I got to do a concentration save.
Dave: How do I do that?
Dave: Remind me.
Kostadis: Roll a D10 and G20 rather and B to 10.
Dave: So, all right.
Kostadis: What?
Kostadis [?]: I beat it.
Kostadis: All right.
Dave: Okay.
Dave: Are you running away?
Kostadis: No, she's not.
Kostadis: The harpy is not running away.
Dave: Oh, you're going to stick right there?
Dave: Perfect.
Dave: Stagic around.
Dave: All right.
Dave: I like it.
Dave: So Vukradin is going to do his double daggers then.
Kostadis: Double daggers.
Kostadis: Well, the harpy is not very intelligent.
Kostadis: He thought you could only cast spells.
Kostadis: Now he's, you know.
Wade: Thought you were a spell slinger.
Dave: He's going to get two attacks.
Dave: Let's see how that goes.
Dave: That's one hit.
Kostadis: All right.
Wade [?]: That's one.
Dave [?]: That's not a hit.
UNKNOWN: That's a crit.
Dave: That's a hit and a half.
Dave: Seven on three.
Dave: That's down to 15.
Dave: And then second attack.
Dave: That's not so miss.
Dave: All right.
Dave: I'll take that.
Kostadis: All right.
Dave: Harpy one.
Dave: Harpy one still singing.
Kostadis: RP one's still singing and attacks the spider.
Kostadis [?]: Let's go.
Kostadis: Because the spider is right there.
Wade: Yep.
Wade [?]: It makes sense.
Wade: Can't hit the spider.
Wade [?]: I'm dodging on the side.
Kostadis: Yeah, no, but you know, it has a certain degree of arachnophobia.
Kostadis: So when it tries to hit the spider, there's a kind of like a reticence.
Kostadis [?]: Does it run away or does it just stay there?
Kostadis: No, it stays there, but there's a certain reticence.
Kostadis: It finds the whole...
Kostadis: It had this whole incident with spiders.
Kostadis [?]: All right.
Kostadis [?]: We attack back.
Dave [?]: Dude, by the way, you have to totally do spider with Spider-Man.
UNKNOWN: You have to do something.
Kostadis [?]: Boer.
Kostadis [?]: Is it a spider with Spider-Man?
Dave: You missed.
Dave: Misses all around.
Wade [?]: Yeah, we're just whiffing at each other.
Wade: As if this combat weren't long enough without the missings.
Dave: All right.
Dave: Brewbarry, you're charmed.
Dave: You're not doing that.
Dave [?]: They have to walk toward number one, we agreed.
Dave [?]: Yeah, you can't really walk towards number one.
Dave: So he does nothing.
Gary: Okay.
Gary: Make a saving throw.
Gary: So I get a save.
Gary: And we'll see if I can roll better.
Wade: A two or a three this time.
Kostadis [?]: Oh, four.
UNKNOWN: Oh, or a five, really.
UNKNOWN: Have you made any attacks or saves in this?
Kostadis [?]: Yeah.
Dave: The entire day.
Dave [?]: Valphine's hit with a couple of crossbow bolts, but a universal whiff.
Dave: Brewbarry has whiffed everything.
Kostadis: Good job.
Dave [?]: We're no longer raging, by the way.
Kostadis: Oh, no.
Kostadis: Yes, we're no longer raging.
UNKNOWN: Yeah.
Kostadis: All right.
Dave: Harpy two.
Kostadis: Harpy two.
Wade [?]: What you gonna do?
Kostadis: Harpy two decides to fly in and attack Valphine.
Dave: Yeah, makes sense.
Dave: No reaction from Brewbarry.
Kostadis: And attacks with her claws.
Gary: AC says miss.
Kostadis: That is a miss.
UNKNOWN: Nice.
Gary: Does she change right away or just stay there?
Kostadis: No, she's staying there.
Kostadis: She doesn't know that you have a sword.
Kostadis: Does she know that?
Kostadis: Yeah.
Kostadis: Oh, she does know that you saw a mace.
Kostadis: She did see you as a mace.
Kostadis: So one, two, three, four.
Kostadis: He flies away here.
Kostadis: You can use your mace.
Kostadis: What?
Kostadis: Me too.
Kostadis: That is a hit.
Kostadis: Three points of damage.
Gary: All right.
Gary [?]: Yeah, and two.
Gary: So then I'm next.
Gary: And then.
Dave: Two is down to four hit points.
Gary: I'll shoot her with a crossbow and then finish her off.
Gary [?]: All right.
Gary [?]: Dead.
Wade: All right.
Wade: One third of the way down.
Gary: Okay.
Gary: And so for the moment, I'm going to go stand right here.
Dave: Nice.
Dave: All right.
Dave: Harpy one is up.
Kostadis: Harpy one is up.
Wade [?]: Don't you mean harpy three?
Kostadis: Harpy three.
Wade [?]: Harpy three is up.
Kostadis: All right.
Wade [?]: Harpy three.
Kostadis: What's RP3 do?
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: RP3 attacks Vukradin again.
Dave: Okay.
Dave: Hit for six.
Dave: I'm feeling weak here, guys.
Dave: And I got to do a concentration save.
Kostadis: Yes.
Dave: Do I get any pluses to that?
Kostadis: It got a constitution.
Dave: Plus one.
Dave: Made it.
Dave [?]: That makes it.
Gary [?]: That's for the silence then, huh?
Dave: That's for the silence.
Dave: We are still silenced.
Dave: All right.
Dave: Vukradin with three hit points and silence concentration.
Dave: And it's facing a harpy.
UNKNOWN: 15 hit points.
Dave: But sure, why not?
Dave: You've got Valphine helping.
Dave: I am pissed off.
Dave: There's a miss.
Dave: Let's try another one.
Dave: Yeah, I'm not feeling so well here, guys.
UNKNOWN: I'm spoozy.
Wade: I mean, I'd like to come protect you, but I also have to help the other guy up here.
Dave: Harpy one.
Wade [?]: Harpy one.
Wade: Come on, share.
Wade: Let's go.
UNKNOWN: Share.
Dave [?]: I think that's.
Dave: Looks like a hit on the spider.
Wade: 16.
Wade: Oh, yeah.
Wade: That's just enough to hit.
Wade: I'm at AC16.
Wade: All right.
Wade: That takes me.
Wade: That gets rid of my bonus hit points.
Wade: Puts me down to 24.
Wade: All right.
Wade: Or temporary.
Dave: Can you change back to human form?
Wade: No, no.
Wade: I think I cheated last time we played just a little bit.
Wade: You don't, as of 2024, they changed Druid a little bit.
Wade: You get bonus hit points or temporary hit points based on your druid level, and you have the full health bar otherwise.
Wade: Okay.
UNKNOWN: All right.
Wade: And then when you get zeroed out, though, it's straight up incapacitate, I think.
Dave: Okay, so you don't revert form anymore.
Wade: I'll double-check that when I get closer to zero, but it is plus temporary hit points based off of your druid level because a lot of people were not happy with getting kicked out of their shapes.
Wade: Particularly some of the smaller ones that are useful.
Wade: Anyway.
Kostadis: No, I actually prefer that.
Wade: I don't care which way it goes.
Wade: I just want to, you know, whatever way the GM wants to play the rules too.
Wade: But the hit points.
Wade: All right.
Kostadis: Who's up next?
Wade: It would be me.
Dave: No.
Dave: Oh, yeah.
Dave: Soma.
Dave: Yeah.
Wade: Yeah.
Wade: And I mean, it's, we're just going to, you know, try and break his concentration again.
Wade: There's a hit.
Wade: There's 12 damage on it.
Wade: That takes him down to six.
Wade: Yeah.
Kostadis [?]: And the singing is over.
Dave [?]: Brewbarry, you're free.
Dave: Hooray.
Dave: Brewbarry can actually attack.
Dave: But can he hit?
Gary: Yeah, that's the key question.
Wade: I see no reason to move or disengage.
Wade: I'm going to see this harpy to the end.
Kostadis [?]: All right.
Wade [?]: Okay.
Gary: Is it my turn now?
Kostadis: Yep.
Gary: All right.
Gary: So can I hit from here with my helmet?
Gary: Definitely.
Kostadis: Yes, you can.
Gary: Without region.
Dave: Yes.
Dave [?]: That is a hit.
Dave: That is a kill.
Kostadis [?]: Okay.
Dave [?]: All right.
Kostadis [?]: Who is last?
Dave: Harpy 3.
Kostadis [?]: Harpy 3.
UNKNOWN: What do you want to do, Harpy 3?
Kostadis: Harpies are not very intelligent.
UNKNOWN: They will keep doing what they were doing last.
Dave: Okay.
Kostadis [?]: Miss.
Dave: Wow.
Kostadis: What was your ear?
Gary: No, we missed something.
UNKNOWN: 13.
Gary [?]: All right, Valphine, you go first.
Gary [?]: Yeah.
Dave: I know.
Dave: Vukradin's up.
Gary: No, Valphine was skipped.
Dave: Oh, I'm sorry.
Gary: Crit for four hit points.
Dave: Four damage.
Gary [?]: Nice.
Gary: Well, you know, like it's getting there.
Dave: Okay.
Dave: Vukradin is up.
Dave [?]: Yes.
Dave: Nope.
Dave: Let's do another one.
Dave [?]: You can drop your silence well if you want.
Wade [?]: No, I'm good.
Dave: Three.
Dave: I like that dagger.
UNKNOWN: Sometimes.
Dave: Some.
Wade: All right.
Wade: Wait.
Wade: Oh, Harpy 1.
Wade: Wait, who's still left alive?
Wade [?]: Harpy 3.
Dave: Yeah.
Dave: Harpy 3 with 8 hit points.
Wade: Yeah, I can clear that, right?
Wade: That's.
Wade: I can go through difficult terrain freely.
UNKNOWN: Yeah, no, I can get in there for sure.
UNKNOWN: I got 40-range movement.
UNKNOWN: Let's go.
Dave [?]: Chompy chompy.
Wade: Roll.
Wade: And I whiff.
Wade: But at least I'm in the fear in the fray now.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis [?]: Yeah, speed 40, climb 40.
Gary [?]: It's fine. Who's next? Brewbarry. Brewbarry. Brewbarry. Brewbarry. Looks at that distance and then, you know, makes it somewhere roughly around here. All right. I can't imagine him jumping down and then running 40 feet to about there.
Dave: You want me to drop the silent spell?
Gary: I guess he can double move.
Gary: Yeah.
Gary [?]: You want me to drop?
Gary: Well, I mean, I'm in mealy now.
Dave: Yeah, but would you be better off with a spell attack?
UNKNOWN: Probably.
Dave: All right, let's drop the silence.
Dave: You can use a spell.
Gary: All
Gary: right, so
Dave [?]: there we go.
Dave: That's X save for four damage.
Dave: Really?
Dave [?]: I could have.
Wade [?]: Given the mace that, hey, don't knock it.
Dave: Four damage.
Wade: It's half his hit points.
Dave: Okay, well.
Dave: All right, you get another attack on Vukradin if you want it, Harpy.
Dave: Or you could attack the spider or Valphine or, you know, you have options.
Kostadis: Yeah, it's really dumb.
Kostadis [?]: Who to attack?
Kostadis: What was that hacking?
Kostadis: It didn't matter.
Dave: It missed.
Kostadis: It missed.
Dave: All right.
Dave: This is when we use Vicious Mockery.
Wade: He's just taunting him on the way down or on the way down.
Dave: Pretty much.
Wade: Yeah, it smells of elderberry.
Wade [?]: 13 save for your life.
Wade: Or four hit points.
Wade: That's here.
Dave: He is mocked to death.
Wade: That Yo Mama joke really cut deep.
Wade [?]: I mean, I would like to retrieve my hand axes.
UNKNOWN: Okay.
Dave: Might want to get more of those.
Dave [?]: Maybe, maybe.
Dave: Yeah.
Dave: I have a whole armory of hand axes available.
Dave [?]: All right.
Kostadis: You do not have infinite hand axes.
Kostadis: Oh.
Dave: Oh, not like arrows?
Kostadis: No, because arrows you can retrieve 50%, and given that most combats have at most 20 rounds, unless you're going out into the wilderness, I'm assuming that you can have 40 arrows and that's it.
Dave: Okay, so.
Kostadis: I mean, obviously, if you go into a large combat where you're killing hundreds of creatures, but then those combats don't exist in this variation of the game.
Gary [?]: Short rest?
Gary: Yeah, and search the bodies.
Kostadis [?]: What are we starting for?
Kostadis: The harpies don't really have anything on them.
Gary: Well, then I will search for my hand axes.
Kostadis: All right, you can grab your hand axes again.
Kostadis: They're like a few feet away from where you threw them because you threw so badly.
Kostadis [?]: Yeah.
Gary: Okay.
Gary: They narrowly missed my own toes.
Kostadis: You're so used to using the halberd action that you kind of threw them like you were using halberds.
Gary [?]: I got two hit points now.
Gary [?]: So that's right.
Wade: Oh, short rest.
Wade [?]: And I took zero damage.
Dave: Yeah, everybody else took like I took three.
Wade [?]: Oh, yeah, you took some damage.
Wade: I took some off of the bonus hit points and then enough to go three.
Wade: Yeah.
Dave [?]: All right.
Wade: And his short rest is more than an hour, right?
Dave: Oh, gentlemen.
Wade [?]: Those 30 minutes.
Dave [?]: 30 minutes.
Dave: Well, they still ship to their doom.
UNKNOWN: We'll no longer taunt them.
UNKNOWN: We did a good thing here today.
Kostadis: All right.
Dave: And also, I don't like harpies singing.
Dave: Their music is just they're not joining the academy, that's for sure.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: Okie dokie.
Kostadis: Let me just read you the description of this area.
Wade: Well, that's enough to heal.
Wade: I needed to heal three.
Kostadis: Ookie.
Wade: You don't recover temporary hit points, right?
UNKNOWN: Those just they never come back.
Dave: Right.
Kostadis: Okay.
Dave [?]: So, yep, this was the rough hewn stairs climb the eastern face of the rocky outcropping.
UNKNOWN: At the top of the stairs, a rocky plateau spreads out some 80 feet above the water.
UNKNOWN: Wooden doors lead, there are wooden doors leading into the area.
Kostadis: They have rusty iron hinges, as well as decorative lightning bolts carved into them.
Dave: Rusty iron hinges.
Dave: Okay.
Dave: Can I go open the door?
Kostadis: Can you open the door?
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: Yes.
Kostadis: Let me just give me one second to read what happens next.
Kostadis: No, I just don't want to pick.
UNKNOWN: Okay.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: Okay.
Kostadis: So the harpies have stopped singing.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: Okay.
Kostadis [?]: That's one way to put it.
Dave: That's one way to put it.
Kostadis: Yeah.
Dave [?]: Well, it's the way.
UNKNOWN: It is what happened.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: Okay.
Kostadis: So you open this door, I presume.
Kostadis: Yeah.
Wade [?]: Oh, yeah.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: Let's see.
Kostadis: This 15-foot-high room is empty.
Kostadis: A dirty window in the south wall through a dirty window in the south wall.
Kostadis: You go here.
Kostadis: You can see something.
Dave: This window.
Kostadis: Yeah.
Dave: What do I see?
Kostadis: You can see wrecks.
Dave: Oh, yes.
Dave: The what the harpies have been doing to the local navy.
Dave: Yes.
Kostadis: All righty.
Dave: So many possessions that must be returned to their rightful owners.
Kostadis: Who are dead underwater?
Dave [?]: It's, you know, what is it?
Dave: They're heirs.
Kostadis [?]: Oh, God.
Dave: Their successors.
Dave: Can't just take things from them.
Dave: Therefore, they died to these evil harpies.
Kostadis: The Order of the Gauntlet is going to be so pleased to have you on their side.
Dave: I don't trust those guys.
Kostadis: Oh, I didn't say it.
Kostadis: I didn't say that.
Dave [?]: You are going to be on your side.
Kostadis: I said they are very pleased.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: There's a door to the there's a just there's a door to the south or to the south.
Kostadis [?]: Yeah.
Kostadis: Door to the south.
Kostadis: All right, T4.
Kostadis: Let me see what
Kostadis: the walls of this 15-foot high room are adorned with frescoes that depict ships being tossed on stormy seas with dark and terrible God looming above them.
Gary [?]: Oh, that's a smile and smiling.
UNKNOWN: Roll a religion check.
Kostadis [?]: All right.
Kostadis [?]: Nope.
Wade: Why did I?
Wade: Oh, yeah.
Dave [?]: Anybody else?
Wade [?]: Anybody else?
Dave: Brewbarry?
Wade [?]: I'm trying.
Wade [?]: Hold on.
Wade: Our cleric's not very religious, is she?
Dave [?]: Wow.
Dave: Nope.
Dave: We got nothing tonight.
Wade [?]: I got a head.
Wade [?]: Well, what you got is it looks pretty, it looks pretty.
Wade: Pretty paintings.
Gary [?]: It's good art.
Gary [?]: Good art.
Dave: Is it frescoed onto the stone, or is it like a piece of art?
Wade: He said fresco, right?
Wade: It's fresco.
Gary [?]: Okay.
Wade: I heard that the description.
Dave: Very nice.
Wade [?]: Yeah, I'm just saying.
Wade [?]: I'd like something like this at the academy.
Dave: I'll remember this.
Dave [?]: You want to chisel out a section of wall and bring it along?
Dave: Well, I don't think.
Dave [?]: I could mold earth it out, right?
Dave: I don't think mold earth is going to be sufficient here.
Wade: Ye have little faith.
Dave: All right.
Dave: Door to the south.
Kostadis: All right, wait.
Dave [?]: Wait, hold on.
UNKNOWN: A stone altar with lightning bolts carved.
UNKNOWN: Set into the west wall is a dirty, salt-encrusted window.
UNKNOWN: A stone altar with lightning bolts carved into it stands against the south wall.
UNKNOWN: A metal rod descends from the ceiling above the altar, splitting in two before it embeds itself into the stone.
Wade: That's like a metal lightning bolt or something.
Wade [?]: The lightning rod, yeah.
Kostadis: A lightning rod.
Dave [?]: Nice.
Dave: Okay.
Dave: Well, do we like want to interact the altar in any way?
Dave: I mean, feel free, guys.
Dave: Go right on.
Gary: Let's check the landing and make sure there's nothing on the landing.
Dave: Do we have a door to the south here?
Wade: Nice view.
Dave: I can see a dead harpy on the parapet.
Wade: Seems like not that long ago I was up there.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: A ledge enclosed by three-foot-high stone retaining wall serves as a nest.
Dave: Oh, the harpy nest?
Kostadis: Yes.
Dave: Oh, this is what you wanted to search, Valphine.
Dave [?]: Can we like torch it?
Kostadis: That's a good idea.
Kostadis: I mean, it stinks.
Kostadis: It does stay.
Kostadis: It does smell.
Wade: I mean, it smells like napalm.
Dave: I think that's a great idea.
Dave: I'll torch it right now.
Dave: I'm not even going to search it.
Wade [?]: I'm just going to get out of there while you torch it.
Wade [?]: I think that's a fantastic idea.
Kostadis: Do you look through anything or do you just torch it?
Gary: I am blowing all my rolls to search it.
Wade [?]: You're just blowing all your rules tonight.
Wade [?]: The good news is you didn't have to blow them very hard because the potion of water breathing was quite obvious.
Kostadis [?]: All right, great.
Kostadis [?]: I don't know.
Dave: Okay, well, we'll need to just determine.
Dave: Maybe we can use like a legend lore spell to determine who owned this potion of water breathing.
Dave: We'll just add that to blood money.
Dave: Consumables.
Wade: That's quite a moral code you got there.
Kostadis: But it's very confused about it.
Dave: I'm confused.
Kostadis: No, I said everybody.
Dave [?]: Everybody else is confused.
Dave: I'm quite confused.
Kostadis: You have to understand, you are engaged in some very revolutionary behavior against the overall world order of this realms.
Wade: Yeah, this is a libertarian paradise, right?
UNKNOWN: Like, just take what you want by force.
Kostadis: No, I wouldn't say it's a libertarian paradise.
Kostadis: It's a liberal, it's not, no, it's, I would say a colonial paradise.
Dave: Colonial.
Dave: Mercantile.
Dave: Yes.
Kostadis: There are people who are considered part of civilized society and people who are not.
Kostadis: All right.
Dave: Well, more blood loot.
Dave: Typical.
Kostadis: All right.
Dave: Let's lift the curse on this tower of storms.
Wade: Oh, yeah.
Wade: It might actually be something with that altar, huh?
Dave: Up the stairs, maybe?
Dave [?]: Oh, wait, hold on.
Kostadis: Oh, right.
Kostadis [?]: We only went through the foyer.
UNKNOWN: You haven't gone upstairs yet.
Kostadis: No, you've not.
Kostadis: There's a door.
Kostadis: There's a stair.
Kostadis: You're going through these doors.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: Hold on.
Kostadis: Enter.
Kostadis: If you enter, you'll see another door.
Dave [?]: Hold on.
Dave: Oh, there's a door to the northeast.
Kostadis [?]: Yes.
Wade [?]: Oh, there's a little like first.
Wade [?]: Sorry.
UNKNOWN: Sorry.
Kostadis [?]: Okay.
Kostadis [?]: Dun dun dun.
Kostadis: Wait, so you go through the door?
Dave: Oh, yeah.
Kostadis: All right, you go through the door.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: Okay, you're going to have to give me one
Dave [?]: 16.
Wade: Oh, yeah.
Wade: I guess that doesn't look like a friendly, does it?
Wade [?]: Nope.
Dave: Let's see.
Dave: Brewbarry, you want to join us inside?
Dave [?]: Yeah.
Dave: Taking the rear guard.
Dave: That's not typical for you.
Kostadis: All right, I'll figure this out later.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: Gone.
Kostadis: Let's see.
Kostadis: You enter this room.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: Why can't you just do things the easy way?
Kostadis: Because that would be telling.
Kostadis: There we go.
Kostadis: All right.
Gary: Are we rolling mischief?
Kostadis: Yes, hold on.
Kostadis: I'm trying to find the for some reason on one of the things.
Kostadis: Yes, a roll for initiative.
Kostadis: I have to re-roll.
Kostadis: I have to reload my browser.
Dave: What are we facing?
Kostadis: One of those weird clerics.
Wade: Oh, geez.
Wade: But he's just alone this time.
Dave: Oh, one of the orcs again?
Kostadis: Yeah, one of the orcs.
Kostadis: And this is the orc that was described as having the conch that belonged to the undead creature.
Dave: Oh, excellent.
Dave: Okay.
Dave: Command holds.
Kostadis: Alrighty.
Kostadis: Okay, resting in his lap is an opalescent conch.
Kostadis: Okay, this 50-foot room has two north-facing windows.
Kostadis: A barnacle encrusted chair stands against the south wall.
Kostadis: Sitting in the chair is Moesko.
Kostadis: All right.
UNKNOWN: He's clad in armor made from a giant octopus hide.
Kostadis: Resting in his lap is an opalescent conch, the one that he took from Myral the Sea Elf.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: Okay.
UNKNOWN: So I suppose we have to roll for initiative.
Wade [?]: We've done that.
Kostadis: I have not.
Kostadis: So I'm just going to have to do this thing.
Dave: Rollo.
Kostadis: Yeah, hold on.
Kostadis: I have to.
Kostadis: Those aren't his ability scores.
Kostadis [?]: Yeah, I know.
Kostadis: So Dexterity is plus one.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: That should be easy enough.
Kostadis: I'm not used to this.
Kostadis: No.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: Let me just do this the old fashioned.
Kostadis: His initiative is a 20.
Kostadis: His armor class is 13.
Kostadis: And his hit points are 58.
Kostadis: 13.
Kostadis: I didn't know.
Dave: AC 13.
Kostadis: Sorry.
Kostadis: AC 13 initiative is an 11.
Kostadis [?]: Oh, 11.
Dave: 11.
Dave: Oh, okay.
Dave [?]: You said 20.
Kostadis: 10, 10.
Kostadis: Sorry, 10, 10.
Kostadis: Sorry, I can't.
Kostadis: I can't hear this.
Dave: It doesn't make a difference, though.
Wade: Yeah, 11 and 10 are the same in this order.
Wade [?]: In this case, it does.
Dave [?]: All right.
Wade [?]: Vukradin, you're up.
Wade: Soma would be up first.
Wade [?]: Soma's up first.
UNKNOWN: Is he sitting?
UNKNOWN: Is he, you know, any sort of...
Kostadis: Yeah, he's sitting.
Kostadis: He packed me sitting.
Kostadis: He sees you.
Kostadis: He's going to get up and attack you.
Kostadis: Usual.
Wade: Does he have any disadvantage for sitting?
Kostadis [?]: No.
Wade: All right.
Wade: Then I'm just going to try to thorn whip him, knock him to his feet.
Wade: Oh, no, that just pulls him.
Wade: That doesn't knock him over, does it?
Kostadis: No, I don't think it does.
Wade: No, I don't think it does.
Wade: I don't know.
Wade: Hardly seems worth doing anything serious to him.
Wade: I'm still going to thorn whip him.
Wade: Or if we're going to poison spray, let's just do that.
Wade: All right, let's go.
Wade: Come on, roll them dice.
Wade: All right.
Wade: Two damage.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: Does not have the poison condition, right?
Wade: No, it does poison damage, not poison condition.
Wade: I believe so.
UNKNOWN: Poison spray.
Dave: Two damage?
Wade: I did two damage.
Dave: Okay.
Wade: I didn't feel like burning a wild shape in here.
UNKNOWN: One lonely guy.
Dave: Make a DC 13 wisdom save.
Kostadis: DC 13, right?
Dave: DC 13 wisdom.
Wade [?]: He's a cleric, right?
Wade: He's probably going to make that.
Kostadis [?]: I don't know.
Kostadis: No, they have really bad signatures.
Kostadis: Who is surprisingly?
Dave: 11.
Dave: That was intelligence.
Dave: It says.
Kostadis: Oh, did I roll in hell?
Kostadis: Sorry.
Dave: Okay, we can go with 11.
UNKNOWN: You roll the 12.
UNKNOWN: You can adjust us accordingly.
Kostadis: I don't know if you have plus plus two.
Dave: Oh, well, then he made it.
Dave [?]: Okay.
Kostadis: All right.
Dave: Stand back here.
Kostadis: Okay, who's next?
Dave: Brewbarry.
Gary: I'll just run in there and melee him.
Gary: Actually, no, I'll run in here and melee him.
Dave: Even better.
Gary [?]: Yes.
Gary: And we can use a second rage.
Gary: A second rage.
Gary: And then we'll go like this.
Gary: Wow.
Gary: Actually, nine.
Gary [?]: Actually, does everybody.
Gary [?]: Good job, Brewbarry.
Dave: You know what?
Dave: I'm sorry.
Dave: It was the silence.
Dave: The fact that you couldn't hear yourself scream, that was.
Gary: That's right.
Gary: That's definitely the problem.
UNKNOWN: Now, Brewbarry is going to have a permanent affectation that silence is bad for it makes him weak.
Kostadis [?]: Silence makes me weak.
Wade: I remember in martial arts, they teach you to, you know, call out with every punch.
Wade: It makes you stronger.
Dave [?]: All right.
Dave [?]: All right, who's next?
Gary [?]: Valphine.
Gary: Valphine.
Gary: What should she do here?
Gary: You know, I think that her mace is more effective than more effective than sacred flame.
Gary: So I'll go with that.
Gary: I guess it means that, yeah, anyway.
Gary: No, for the first attack, I'll just use a crossbow.
Gary: Yeah, we'll go here and there and that.
UNKNOWN: Okay.
Kostadis: Six points of damage.
Gary: Damage.
Gary: I'll put it in.
Kostadis: Yep, next.
Kostadis: Okay.
Dave: The orc is up.
Kostadis: The orc is up.
Kostadis: Anchorite.
Kostadis: That's the word I'm looking for.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: Casts lightning bolt.
Wade: That's probably not going to be good.
Wade [?]: That seems bad.
Wade [?]: Yeah.
Wade [?]: TPK here.
Gary [?]: Dex saves for everybody.
Kostadis: What?
Gary: TPK right here.
Dave: Nah, not yet.
Dave: It doesn't have us all in a straight line.
Dave: I made my save.
Dave: Yeah.
Kostadis: So the three, everybody but Brewbarry.
Kostadis: Oh, everyone.
Kostadis: Yeah.
Kostadis: It's everybody but Brewbarry.
Kostadis: All right.
Gary: And the DC is what?
Kostadis: 12.
Wade [?]: Yeah.
Wade [?]: That's how much damage coming our way.
Kostadis: I'm about to find out.
Kostadis: Oh, Lord.
Wade [?]: No, no.
Kostadis: Last time.
Dave: 8d6?
Kostadis: Yeah.
Kostadis: Well, it's not letting me roll it, so 8d6 by hand.
Kostadis: 25.
Dave: 25 half damage is 12.
Kostadis: Yes.
Dave: Okay, take 12.
Dave: Ooh, I'm down to four.
Dave: Soma, you're down to two.
Wade: Yep.
Wade [?]: Still standing.
Kostadis: What?
Dave: Oh, but I want to do my attack.
Dave: I was so excited for it.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: So we could go.
Kostadis: We could go a few more rounds.
Kostadis: We could go one more round.
Wade [?]: So you're up.
Wade: Yeah, that's that.
Wade: Now I do want to burn the wild shape charge coming out as a spider.
Dave: Yeah.
Wade: So I'm now at 11 hit points.
Wade [?]: No bear this time.
Wade: I can't fit bear in here.
Wade: Bear is large.
Wade [?]: Should we move?
Wade: No, we're committed now, right?
Gary: Want me to move here and then you can get the bear in there?
Wade: It's not your turn.
Wade [?]: Well, I mean, it was my turn earlier, but I mean, if you could, yeah, a bear would be a little more appropriate.
Wade: Yes.
Wade: Give me a bear icon quickly.
Kostadis: Oh, no.
Kostadis: Okay, why don't you move your character and get bear?
Wade: I'll just say I'm bear in this two by two area.
Wade: Where is?
Wade: Oh, I have to load up bear.
Wade: God darn it.
Wade: Brown bear.
Wade: Important thing is brown bear gets multi-attack.
Wade: So we're just going to hit both of these.
Dave: Hit.
Wade: 20 damage.
Dave: 20.
UNKNOWN: Yay, bear.
UNKNOWN: Rar.
Wade: 21.
Kostadis: Is it what kind of bear is it?
Kostadis [?]: Cave Bear?
Kostadis [?]: Brown bear?
Wade: Brown bear.
Dave: The best bear.
Dave: Best kind of bear.
Wade: Oh, right.
Wade: The images on here are useless.
Wade: Half the monsters, half.
Wade: I still can't select them.
Wade: Anyway, Vukradin you're up, right?
Dave: All right.
Dave: Can you give me a five-foot cube, please?
Kostadis: Five-foot cube?
Kostadis: Just okay, five-foot cube.
Kostadis: You should be able to actually see it yourself.
Dave: Cool.
Kostadis [?]: Not see.
Dave: Rectangle.
Dave: Looks like that, yes?
Kostadis: Yeah.
Dave: Okay, I'm going to now select that.
Dave: I'm going to position it right there.
Dave: Right there.
Kostadis: Okay.
Dave: Cloud of daggers takes nine damage, and now that he's trapped in there, he can take nine damage on every round.
Dave [?]: Why is he trapped in there?
Wade [?]: Well, he's got to get a bear.
Kostadis: Okay.
Wade: There's a round bear in his way, but he's just going to lightning bolt it to death, and that'll kill it.
Dave: Oh, he's at 12.
Dave: Let me actually double-check the rule, make sure there isn't something I missed on this.
UNKNOWN: If it enters the cube or ends its turn there, or if the cube moves into its space.
UNKNOWN: Okay, so the cube takes this damage once per turn.
Dave: And it's 44 each time it takes damage.
Dave: Okay.
Gary [?]: Done.
Gary: Would you like to move left three squares?
Kostadis [?]: Where'd my bear go?
Dave [?]: Is it a hold on?
Dave [?]: Is it a I would
Dave: the bear go?
Gary: Yeah, we lost the bear.
Wade [?]: Oh, you did?
Wade [?]: Yeah.
Wade [?]: I mean, you never gave me control, but now it's gone.
Dave: Bear has disappeared.
Dave [?]: I don't know.
Kostadis: Hold on.
Kostadis: I was futzing with trying to get things to work, and I thought I got it to work.
Kostadis: Do you see?
Kostadis: You see no bear, right?
Kostadis: That's fine.
Dave [?]: I see no bear.
Dave: No bear.
Dave: Can you undo?
Kostadis: Yeah, I have to.
Kostadis: I'll get the bear.
Kostadis: There you go.
Kostadis: First of all, let's get the appropriate bear.
Wade: All right.
Wade: I see a whisper of a bear and cannot get a bear.
Wade: I should need to figure out how to do this without you.
Dave [?]: Yeah.
Wade: I should be able to.
Wade: I just don't know what to losing you.
Dave: Losing you, Kostas.
Dave: The tubes are clogged.
Dave [?]: It's a series of tubes.
Dave: Switch to the truck, man.
Wade [?]: Testing.
Wade: It's just Kostas.
Dave: Yeah, it's just Kostas.
Dave: It's a sign.
Dave: Well, it lasted until time.
Dave: So that's good.
Dave: Well, maybe Brewbarry or Valphine can finish him off.
Dave: Because another lightning bolt is going to be deadly.
Dave [?]: Lightning will be an issue.
Dave: Another lightning bolt will not go well.
Dave: There will be
Dave: three characters down.
Gary [?]: And that will be painful.
Gary: Well, maybe rather than stepping three scores left, you should step into the maybe I should step out of the room.
Dave: Yeah, maybe I should go over here.
Gary: You don't have to maintain sight line to your diagram's team.
Dave: No, I don't.
Dave: Well, he says his internet died.
Dave: So I think we should just call it.
Dave: Thanks, guys.
UNKNOWN: See you next week.
UNKNOWN: Oh, are you back?
Kostadis: Yeah, yeah, back.
Kostadis: There's just an internet flux.
Dave: That's how things go in Greece.
Kostadis: That's how things go everywhere.
Dave: Fair.
Kostadis: But on Centrini, when I have.
Kostadis: So my house in Centrini has like eight rooms, and I have like lots of nieces and nephews and cousins and relatives.
Kostadis: And so I had to buy an industrial strength router to deal with all the DHL connections people were creating.
Kostadis: Not the DHL connections, the VPN?
Dave: No, no.
Kostadis: The word was DHCP.
Kostadis: That's what I'm looking for.
Dave [?]: Oh, DACES.
Kostadis: Yeah.
Kostadis: So everybody was like, I had so many people, players, people joining that last that I had to buy a commercial grade DHC router to deal with all the DHCP connections.
Kostadis: It's pretty funny because it was pretty funny because when they were five years ago, when they didn't all have cell phones and gadgets, things worked fine.
UNKNOWN: Then three years ago, things started to be flaky.
Kostadis: And two years ago, it was like I had to hand out static IP addresses to people.
Gary [?]: Crazy.
Gary [?]: So, yeah.
Kostadis: Turns out if you need more than 50 DHCP addresses, you need to buy yourself an expensive router.
Wade: I just use a Linux server.
Kostadis: Yeah, the nice thing about a commercial router is that I can pay someone in Centrini to maintain it.
Kostadis: So when my dad is here and he doesn't get me do anything, it can be taken care of.
Dave: Okay, Brewbarry is up.
Kostadis: But I do agree a Linux server would have been cheaper.
Dave: Yeah.
Kostadis: Lord, it would have been cheaper.
Dave [?]: All right.
Dave: Not looking good, guys.
Dave: Brewbarry back to the night.
Gary: Yeah, though, yeah.
Gary: All right.
Gary: Valphine, it will.
UNKNOWN: Valphine, you got to do 12 damage or we're really screwed.
Dave: Or a silent spell or something that's going to stop him from casting lightning bolt.
Gary: I don't know if I can do that, but we'll see.
Gary: Looking object.
Gary: No?
Gary: Yeah.
Gary: How about a across fobolt?
UNKNOWN: That's not going to be enough.
Dave: But sure.
Gary: And we will go with that.
Gary: Let's do five damage and then I will step out of the room.
Dave: Good plan.
Wade: Everyone's just abandoning the bear.
Wade [?]: The bear will be fine.
Wade: Mama Bear go down.
Wade [?]: Brewbarry is fine.
Dave: All right.
Dave: Do you have another lightning bolt?
Kostadis: No, I don't.
UNKNOWN: That's what I was kind of smiling.
UNKNOWN: Oh, geez.
Dave: That's fine.
Kostadis: I'm just going, okay.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: So
Dave: Thunder Wave.
Dave: Oh, I like that one.
Kostadis: 2v8.
Wade: I can survive this.
Wade: Yeah.
Wade: Maybe.
Wade [?]: Maybe.
Wade: And it's pushed 10 feet.
Wade: Ooh.
Kostadis: Rolling of dice is taking a while.
Wade: Is there a save on?
Wade: Points of damage.
Wade: Oh, yeah, it is.
Wade: Constitution save.
Wade: All right.
Wade: Well, I got some help there.
Kostadis: A save on.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: Steve.
Wade [?]: Why don't I say that?
Wade [?]: Pushed back.
Wade: What is the difficulty?
Dave: You're pushed back.
Wade [?]: Are you going to move?
Dave: Are you going to move out of the cloud?
Wade [?]: What's the DC?
Wade [?]: Does he take damage from what's the difficulty?
Dave: Maybe 12 or 13.
Wade: Oh, yeah, then I definitely have to.
Gary [?]: 12.
Gary [?]: Yeah.
Gary: So nice DC points.
Gary: And if you leave that square, I'll get to attack you.
Kostadis: Well, yes, I know.
Dave: He moved out of the cloud, so Brewbarry, you're up.
Dave: Do your attack.
Dave: Maybe you can finish him.
Dave: He's down to three hit points.
Wade: No rage bonus?
Wade [?]: Yes, rage bonus.
Wade: Which is what?
Dave: Two?
Dave: Two.
UNKNOWN: Yeah.
Wade: So he's down to one hit point.
Dave: Down to one hit point?
Wade: All right.
Wade: Can I attack to end the night?
Wade [?]: Please.
Wade: Let's see if I can hit once on one of these two tries.
Dave: Dead.
Wade [?]: Dead?
Dave [?]: Yes.
UNKNOWN: I mean, he needed one hit point.
UNKNOWN: I think I did 13.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: All right, guys.
Kostadis: We will stop here.
Kostadis [?]: Okay.
Wade: Pick up the loot and the, yeah, we'll figure out what that conch is and everything next week.
Dave [?]: All right.
UNKNOWN: Excellent.
UNKNOWN: It was great.
UNKNOWN: I'm glad I finally figured out how to play D.
Wade: Yeah, if only Zoom worked.
Wade: Good luck with the internet, Costano.
Dave: Good luck with your internet.
Dave: Your island internet.
UNKNOWN: All right.
UNKNOWN: Bye, guys.
Kostadis: Indy from Greece.